module.exports = {
    'Note Names': [
        'C', 'D♭', 'D', 'E♭', 'E', 'F', 'G♭', 'G', 'A♭', 'A', 'B♭', 'B'
    ],
    'Chords': [
        { question: 'C', answer: ['C', 'E', 'G'] },
        { question: 'D♭', answer: ['D♭', 'F', 'A♭'] },
        { question: 'D', answer: ['D', 'G♭', 'A'] },
        { question: 'E♭', answer: ['E♭', 'G', 'B♭'] },
        { question: 'E', answer: ['E', 'A♭', 'B'] },
        { question: 'F', answer: ['F', 'A', 'C'] },
        { question: 'G♭', answer: ['G♭', 'B♭', 'D♭'] },
        { question: 'G', answer: ['G', 'B', 'D'] },
        { question: 'A♭', answer: ['A♭', 'C', 'E♭'] },
        { question: 'A', answer: ['A', 'D♭', 'E'] },
        { question: 'B♭', answer: ['B♭', 'D', 'F'] },
        { question: 'B', answer: ['B', 'E♭', 'G♭'] }
    ],
    'Intervals': [
        { question: 'half step', answer: 'D♭' },
        { question: 'full step', answer: 'D' },
        { question: 'minor third', answer: 'E♭' },
        { question: 'major third', answer: 'E' },
        { question: 'perfect fourth', answer: 'F' },
        { question: 'tritone', answer: 'G♭' },
        { question: 'perfect fifth', answer: 'G' },
        { question: 'minor sixth', answer: 'A♭' },
        { question: 'major sixth', answer: 'A' },
        { question: 'minor seventh', answer: 'B♭' },
        { question: 'major seventh', answer: 'B' },
        { question: 'octave', answer: 'C' }
    ]
};